Ta-da! Here it is!
It's so good! Really!
I thought this is the best place for the biggest screen of Somat...
Hello!
I'm Mizuki Hiraoka from Hyuhizaka 46.
Hi, I'm Mizuki Hiraoka from Hinatazaka-46.
Today...
What a surprise!
Anko, who I love so much
I'm going to take a YouTube video with my favorite
I'm going to make a YouTube video with my beloved Anko.
Thank you very much!
Last time was in September.
I went to Nagoya.
I went to three shops...
I went to three stores.
And...
I've been on YouTube full of happiness.
But today, what a surprise!
Mitsuki Hiraoka researched
Strawberry Daifuku in Tokyo!
Mitsuki Hiraoka has found the top 3 best strawberry daifuku in Tokyo!
Yay!
Thank you very much!
Last time, I visited 3 stores.
But this time, it's like a Japanese-style house.
but this time we're going to eat at a place that looks like a Japanese-style house
This time, we will eat at a Japanese style house like this.
Like this.
Ume blossoms are in bloom.
Plum blossoms are in bloom.
It's nice.
Plum blossoms.
They bloom a little earlier than cherry blossoms.
They're perfect for Japanese sweets.
It's like eating Daifuku with strawberries.
That's an exaggeration.
In such a beautiful place.
I'd like to enjoy it with a spring breeze.
I'd like to eat it.
Yes, sir!
Let's start with the first one!
The first one is Akasaka Aono's strawberry daifuku!
The strawberries are small and can be eaten in one bite.
It seems to be very popular among women!
So cute!
It's like Daifuku is about to eat a strawberry!
Thank you for watching!
And what a surprise, I prepared tea for you today!
I'm a cat person, so I'm going to put some tea in it and leave it for a while.
I'm going to have some of this in a little bit.
I'm looking forward to it!
Oh, it's so good!
Bon appétit!
Mmm.
Yum.
Delicious.
Kosian.
The strawberries are really small.
You can enjoy the strawberries in one bite.
It's a very smooth Kosian.
Kocian varies a lot depending on the amount of water.
The smoothness, the looseness, the moistness...
or moistness...
This is a very smooth Koschian.
Kosian.
The rice cake part of this Daifuku is soft.
There are two types, one is dumpling-like and elastic, and the other is very soft.
And the other is very soft.
There are two types of mochi.
This one is a little stretchy like a Haniujyu-mochi type rice cake.
This one is a little stretchy like a Haniujyu-mochi.
I just ate all the strawberries
I ate them all in one bite.
From here on...
I'd like to enjoy the rice cake and red bean paste even more
I'd like to eat it while enjoying this rice cake and red bean paste even more.
Yum!
Delicious!
Thank you for watching!
It's really delicious!
Try just eating this kosian and the rice cake.
The smoothness of the kosian and the softness of the rice cake are so exquisite.
It's like I was doing this with a very soft blanket in winter
It's like a very soft blanket in winter and a very soft blanket in winter.
Can you tell?
It's like the best match for chimilas!
Thank you for watching!
Yes, it's delicious!
First, Akasaka Ohno's strawberry daifuku...
Very elegant!
The strawberries were small and easy to eat.
The rice cake and red bean paste were very smooth.
Everything was mixed well together.
It was a very elegant strawberry daifuku!
Thank you very much!
Now, let's have the second one!
Strawberry snow daifuku from Ginza Suzuya Sekkado!
Here it is!
Isn't this cute?
It looks like it would be popular with the girls.
This one, too, is a very different strawberry daifuku from the first one!
Ta-daifuku!
Can you tell? If you have a good intuition, you may have already noticed...
There is no black shadow of red bean paste inside, which means this is a white bean paste.
It's strawberry daifuku with white bean jam!
This is the fifth Anko product I've eaten since the last time, and it's my first white Anko!
I've seen a video of making white bean paste. It's made from white beans.
White beans are softer than azuki beans.
The white beans are softer than azuki beans, so when it comes to white bean paste, it is softer than normal bean paste.
So I think it will be soft like snow.
Bon appétit!
Really? I can't believe it...
I don't know.
It's the softest thing I've ever had.
I wonder if Rina's cheeks are this soft.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Thank you for watching!
Hmmm...
I see.
I'm really impressed.
The white bean paste is...
As I said at the beginning.
It's really soft and melty.
It's so soft and melt-in-your-mouth.
From inside the Daifuku
from inside the Daifuku
It's so smooth
Soft is the first thing that comes to mind.
The first thing that comes to mind is the softness.
When you bite into this Daifuku
the first thing that comes to mind is the dumpling type
It's a type of Daifuku that has a good bite.
Daifuku is a type of dumpling
The texture of the Daifuku has a nice bite to it
texture and
and the extremely soft
and soft white bean paste
and the freshness of strawberries
It's so much fun!
With that one bite
Mmmm...
Thank you for watching!
I think I made a pretty good choice!
The Strawberry Snow Daifuku was very delicious!
Now let's go to the third one!
The third one is the Strawberry Mame Daifuku from Ohmakudama-ya!
Ta-da!
I love Mame Daifuku!
I also love strawberry daifuku!
I thought, "Of course it's delicious when they are combined together!
Well, let's try it!
But it's so big, where are the strawberries?
Bon appétit!
Wow, it's delicious!
Yum!
It's so good! It really is!
First of all, after such a great reaction
I haven't gotten to the strawberries yet.
I just ate a piece of Daifuku (bean-stuffed rice cake).
This rice cake is also rather crispy, but heavy.
But it's heavy and quite chewy.
I haven't got to the strawberries yet after all this talking.
I'm going to go now.
Mmm...
Mmmm!
Thank you for watching!
The sweet bean paste is fresh.
and the sweetness is quite moderate.
I think the sweet bean paste flavor comes through well.
Also, since it's a mame daifuku, there's this red pea around it.
The red peas around the bean paste do not fight with the lush bean paste.
When you bite into it, the red peas come together with the sweet bean paste.
It's very tasty, just the way I like it!
Everyone uu te
är
Cryptic
While tasting it, I was at the peak of my happiness.
I was at the height of my happiness.
And I was thinking...
I thought this is the best place for the biggest screen of Soma Lights.
There was a moment when I felt the happiest since I became an idol.
The moment when I met my seniors for the first time.
I was so nervous that I didn't know what to do.
I was so nervous, and I was wondering what to do, but if I were to put a value on happiness, I would say that I was very happy.
This moment and this moment might be a little bit in the same line.
I'm so happy that this moment and this moment might be in the same line.
I'm really happy.
It's not something to compare.
But we have different vectors.
But it's the peak of happiness that you can feel with your taste buds.
I've just experienced the peak of happiness.
I want everyone to taste it!
I chose strawberry daifuku this time.
My top three favorite Japanese sweets are
Dorayaki, Taiyaki and Strawberry Daifuku!
Maybe someday...
I've always wanted to try dorayaki and taiyaki.
I've always wanted to eat them.
Dorayaki...
There are so many places to eat them.
I've eaten them.
So, out of the ones that I've actually eaten
I'd like to recommend the best three that I've really enjoyed.
I'd like to recommend the best three that I've actually eaten.
I'd like to recommend some of the best 3 that I've actually eaten.
I would like to continue to eat
I would like to continue to eat well and happily.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating
Thank you very much!
See you soon!